Keep running along, watch as we pass by,
as we raise our flag, up high in the sky.
Alright,
here we go now, sailing through the
endless ocean, facing all that comes by.
Let's look for our treasure, nobody has
ever got to witness with their own eyes.
All we have to do is keep believing in our
dreams, And let our heart lead the way!
Then once we got all the
others left is to go,
When we face the dark and stormy weather?
Keep the pace, we'll
link our hearts together!
Then I'm sure we'll make it through!
No matter what!
Keep running along, keep running along!
Start raising our flag as we journey on!
Though our chances are close to
none, We won't back down from anyone!
Let's start off the chase,
let's start off the chase!
Toward our own dreams,
while keeping the pace!
With a compass pointing to our goal!
We won't stop till we've
gone around the world!
Start me up!
Keep running along, keep running along!
And we'll never stop,
till we're at the top!
There's no way that we'll ever quit!
Won't keep heading for tomorrow!
Let's start up the chase!
I see through your eyes!
What we'll have to face!
All the memories will stay in our hearts!
We'll never let them go!
Brand new world!
Let's start me up!
Hey, look!
They're opening!
The Gates of Justice are really opening!
You're right!
In all my years here, this is the
first time it's ever happened!
I've never even heard
of it happening before!
We must be letting the
battleships from the headquarters
through the Buster Call
is about to let loose
Crap I don't like this.
Granny Kokoro said the Gates of Justice
never open all the way like that
This Buster Call thing
must be really bad Even
the Marines are in a
panic to get out of here.
The Straw Hats picked a fight
with the whole world They
might really burn down the
whole island to get at them
Bring it in there, bro!
Don't die!
Yeah!
You too, Straw Hat! Kill me!
Robin will be fine.
I know Franky can take care of her.
I was careless.
Yes, this new power of
his took me by surprise.
Whatever you're doing seems
to be taking its toll.
In shame, the fight was
just getting interesting.
I don't care what happens.
As long as I can beat you.
I see.
How stubborn.
Almost there!
Don't you dare leave yet, Nico Robin!
Guards, on to the bridge!
Yes, sir!
All right, men. Ready? Good!
Because Chief Spondheim
is on his way as we speak.
He's delivering an
especially heinous criminal
across the bridge from the Tower of Law.
This doesn't happen often,
so I want all marines
from the escort ships
and all guards from the
gate here in top form!
Give them the best
dance salute you've got!
Would you look at that!
All lined up and ready to sail!
Not a thing left to stop me!
Oh, I almost forgot.
There's a surprise waiting
for your little friends.
You see,
before we cross the bridge,
I set up a landmine at the top
of those stairs right over there.
So in the unlikely event that someone
actually does come to save you,
they and the stairs will both go BOOM!
Quite the elegant
solution, don't you think?
Well, I'm excited at least.
Though I suppose neither of us
should get our hopes up too much,
Seeing as how no one will be coming
to help you in the first place!
I won't go through that gate.
What?
I still believe they'll come to
save me They're not coming, okay?
Gee, shut up!
They'll be burned to a crisp Just like
everything else in the Buster Calls path.
You got that?
Rather convenient, really.
Every humiliation I've suffered,
including them shooting down our flag,
will be erased as well.
Just like before, 20 years ago, when
that marine giant attacked us in Ohala.
Now it's time to walk.
That means on your own two feet, damn it.
Saul.
Hurry up!
Are you okay, chief?
Do you need help?
No, I don't need any help.
Dammit, I'm a friggin' hero!
If you thought I didn't know anything
about that, then you're dead wrong.
Your old friend Jaguar de Sol was a
vice-admiral before he betrayed us.
Your mother, Olvia, was an archaeologist.
And I know about your
hometown of Ohara as well.
Quite the tragic tale, isn't it?
And why do I know all this?
Well, it's quite simple.
Because the man who
commanded the raid on Ohara,
uncovered their crimes, then blew the
island to smithereens with a Buster Call?
was the chief of CP9 who preceded me!
Otherwise known as my father, Spandine!
Well, scholars of Ohara, I'm afraid your
death sentence has already been decided.
Kill him!
You left us no choice.
Ohara knows too much.
I invoke the Buster Call.
And that's a wrap.
Hurry, take her and go, Saul
Are you sure? Yeah.
Stop it, I want to stay with you, mommy!
I was happy to hear
you call me back again.
Thank you.
From now on.
For my sake as well.
You must live, Robin!
At the time, they thought that everyone
in Ohara had been nicely eliminated.
But they found out later that one little
brat had slipped through their fingers.
So, how was it?
Running from one money-grubbing
adult to the next,
hoping you weren't either
killed or sold out.
Not a single person you
could trust no matter where
you went nowhere to lay your
little head down in peace
nothing to eat what a vile
and wretched existence
you've had why it's too
appalling to even think about
sad enough to make you cry huh 20 years
ago my old man put that bounty on your
little hand, all for world peace.
Show some gratitude, will you?
Now we finally have our happy ending.
The son completes the father's crusade
against the devils of Ohara, and the
wrongs of 20 years ago have
been made right at last.
Ohara is dead!
Don't cry Robin, but be proud.
Your mama's a wonderful woman.
Ohara's a wonderful place.
You gotta remember that.
It's up to you to pass it on, okay.
Ohara was so brave.
They fought against the whole world.
Ohara won't die as long as I live. Yeah?
And how long is that going to be? Huh?
Whoa!
The egg went off!
Cutty Flam!
What is he doing here?
Well, no harm done.
He fell for the landmine. Idiot!
Serves you right!
He came to rescue me still that was close
it's a good thing i had my backup plan.
Come on let's go i'm so angry i can't
even speak all right marine set sail.
We're getting out of here
now understood sir everyone
move yes sir i can't hold
back the tears anymore?
Watch carefully men because you're about
to witness the first step of a hero!
that is destined to go down in history!
Are you okay, Chief? What happened?
He was hit! We're under attack!
There's no one on the bridge but us!
No!
They must be hiding somewhere!
Everyone start searching!
But where?
Huh?
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
Fight back!
Don't just stand there!
Betrayed, sir, but we don't
know where the enemy's at!
There!
he's standing on top of the
tower of law what's he doing
up there it's so far away
How the hell's he hitting us?
Is he using a slingshot?
This guy's a monster.
The wind runs like crazy, and
he's all the way over there,
but he's still hitting
his mark every time.
Thank you, Long Nose.
Bam, eat that.
Our sniper is number one.
Serves you right, bastards.
Come on, Robin, run!
I can do without the singing, I think.
Team!
Damn it!
What are you idiots doing?
Shoot that guy already!
We're trying,
sir, but he's too far away for our bullets
to reach, let alone to actually hit him.
I hate to say it, but he's
got us totally outclassed!
Nico Robin is getting away!
Then stop her!
Shoot her down, sir.
Shoot her just dead
enough to keep her alive
Who the hell is that?
Franky...
Bullets are no problem
when you're made of iron.
But that landmine wasn't
very nice, Spanda.
Franky!
Come in, Franky!
Do you read me?
This is Sniper King! Huh?
Yeah, I can read you
loud and clear, but...
How?
I got the snail from Nami.
Anyway, turn around.
There should be a red bundle
on the ground next to you.
Red bundle?
Oh, I see it. Good.
It has two keys inside.
Together with the ones you have,
that should be all of them.
How did they get the keys?
And my mission is complete.
Nice work.
All right, then. Let's go.
Number one, number three,
number four, number five.
We got it!
No way!
This can't be happening to me!
Oh, hold on.
We're not in the clear yet. But wait!
That means...
They really did it?
A bunch of useless pirates
beat every last member of CP9?
No, that can't be right.
They must have just stolen
the keys and run away!
Hey, bunch of cheaters!
Okay, we got it!
Hey, you hear me?
We got the handcuffs off
Robin, no problem! Yes!
Thank you, Longhouse.
That was wonderful.
It was the least I could do.
The true heroes are those who fought
to retrieve those keys from the enemy.
The Straw Hats will be
proud to have you back.
Hold your head up high and meet them
with a smile when all of this has ended.
Right.
No, c 'est fleur.
What the?
Slap.
I've been waiting a long time to do this.
Are you okay, chief?
All right, let's move.
Get your asses over here.
I'll get everything ready for you.
We're gonna bail. Roger!
Get down here already, Sniper King.
The prisoners escaped from the
same prism stone handcuffs.
Regroup and recapture her!
Everything went according to my plan.
What's that?
I swear I heard something.
What the hell was that?
The battleships are firing on us?
I took out the stockade!
Vice Admiral,
our cannon fire landed a
direct hit on the stockade
at four o 'clock in
front of the main island.
So, what's your point?
Um?
Is there any reason why
that should matter to me?
Oh, uh, I guess not, sir.
This is a thorough, indiscriminate attack.
I only care if we don't hit something.
Right.
Our mission is to bomb everything
on this island into the sea.
They blew a hole in the
fence around the island.
It was a pretty massive explosion.
They've got enough room to steer a whole
fleet through there and
rain fire all over us.
And take a look at that.
The whirlpools that usually surround
the island have completely vanished.
If they aren't around to keep ships out
and the Gates of Justice are wide open,
there's nothing to stop the attacks.
I guess those whirlpools were
only there because the gates
were blocking the flow of
the current to the waterfall.
So now that the gates are open,
the current is a straight
shot to the falls
and is smooth sailing for
all those battleships.
Things are about to get ugly.
Yeah, we better get
moving while we still can.
Hey, Sniper King!
Things have gotten serious!
Hurry up and jump down from there!
Is that supposed to be a joke? First off,
I don't have the same kind of freakish
superhuman strength that you guys have,
all right?
And while perfectly ample, my
bravery is not the life-risking kind.
In case you haven't noticed, I'm a
normal superhero, not a super-superhero!
No, Usopp!
They bombed the Tower of Law!
Longnose was...
You think they hit him?
They took out the Tower of Law!
It's falling over here!
Let's just hope those guys are okay.
That wasn't just some
accidental explosion up there!
You're right!
I think we're under attack!
We gotta get off this damn island!
Oh, my God.
He...
He can't be...
Where are you, Usopp?
Someone say my name!
Why'd you make us think you were dead?
You guys couldn't even be bothered to catch
a hero who's plunged off an exploding,
falling building?
Some friends you are!
Hey Franky Robin we're all okay over
here and we're heading your way now?
Thank goodness well we
better get things in order
how you feeling right now
you think you're up for
a fight of course what
the hell are you waiting
for wait them out before
their backup arrives yes
sir you noticed the ship
on the other side of
the bridge right i'm
thinking it's our best chance
to get out of this mess
well we're already wanted
criminals we might as
well steal Take them down!
Now raise them!
Take them down!
I figure this much
It's like you're doping
yourself with your own blood
You use your legs as pumps
to accelerate your blood flow
Good thing you're not an ordinary
human That kind of blood pressure would
make your heart burst But since your
internal organs are made of rubber,
you can handle it A technique only
someone like you could use But
that doesn't mean you should it's
obvious that you're pushing your
body too far and I doubt that you
can take much more not very clever
are you you're shortening your own
lifespan just for a few minutes of
strength it's better than letting
you take away everything I care
about I'll do anything to keep that
from happening but you've still lost
even if you do defeat me you must
have felt that explosion earlier
it's a pretty safe bet that was a
battleship launching a warm-up shot
Shouldn't be too much longer before
they start a full-scale bombardment.
And for all we know, your friends at
the Tower of Law could be dead already.
Maybe they got out.
Maybe they're already running
through the underground
passageways trying to get
here in time to help you.
Ha.
Tempest!
What did you do?
You might defeat me,
but you can't stop this
seawater from flooding the
tunnel and drowning anyone
who happens to be in there.
You bastard!
Face the facts, Straw Hat.
Nothing's going your way.
But don't let me stop you from trying.
I'm interested to see
how far you'll go in your
misguided attempts to
save your little friends.
This isn't a game we're playing, dammit!
Kokoro! Chimney! Kenpo!
Thanks for leaving the guide marks!
Yay!
It's the pirate lady! Yeah! Yeah!
Did you guys feel that giant tremor?
Sounds like the party's
starting up there for sure!
Cannon fire! Cannon fire!
Speed it up, you goons!
I want Nico Robin captured
on that ship, Po' Sexy!
We don't have long!
The battleships are coming!
Actually, we're out of time, sir.
What did you say?
Look behind the phone!
The ships are here!
Hey!
Why are you running?
Get back here!
Oh, no.
You asked for it, Nico Robin.
The Buster Call is here!
The invocation of merciless death,
the Buster Call has finally begun!